Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
The Bazaar, featuring Barbara Foster, Larry Mizrahi, Bonnie Garcia, Sheila Devine, Donna Cameron, Ana Klingman, Angelo Jannuzzi, Lorna Bieber, Maija Beeton, and Patrick Mills and others, February 13 - 27.
Teichert, Sabine "Pantimento", March 2-15.
Wewer, Savine "Paintings and Collages", March 2-15
3rd Annual Expressions Afrikan, group exhibition, March 16 - 29.
Corn, Thom, "The Real Black Action", installation, March 16 - 29.
Schlesinger, Christina, "The Madonna Rising Amid Graffiti", mural, March 19 - April 25..
Wibmer, Margret, "Paintings and Sculptures", March 29 - April 5.
Nebeska, Eva, "Paintings", April 2 - 30
Spring Mysteries: The Lesser & Greater Transformateur des Refuser, by Maggie Ens and Charlie Morrow, April 9 - 16
Close group exhibition featuring Amir Bey, Aliz du Serech, Elizabeth Rodriguez, Clarissa Sligh, and Chrysanne Stathacos. April 23 - May 7
Ros, Moses "The Cutting Edge", May 7 - May 28
Waxberg, Richard "Recent Paintings", May 14 - June 4
Lens, Jessica "The Sun, the Moon and the Connected Stars... ", installation, June 15 - 28.
Smith, Barbara "Pageant of the Holy Squash", December.
1989-1990
Roan, Bart: exibition, January.
Misera, Lisi: installation on facade of Fashion Moda, June - October.
Toral, Tabo: Installation, ongoing since June 1989
English, Ron: Installation, October 1989 - June 90
Exhibition/Fundraiser, featuring Rigoberto Torres, Chuck Hardgrove, MarkKostabi, Ronnie Cutrone, Ricky Prol, Crash, Daze, Ariel Jordan, Wendy Hoffmann, Tabo Toral, Ron English, and others. December 1989 - January 1990
1991
Toral, Tabo: Installation, ongoing.
Eins, Stefan: Performance, March 1991
Exhibition/Fundraiser at Brooke Alexander Gallery, featuring Donald Baechler, Joseph Kosuth, Claes Oldenburg, Tom Otterness, May Ray, Kenny Scharf, and Kiki Smith, March 1991.
The South Bronx Show, featuring Agent, Tony Buczko, Amy Chailkin, Andre Charles, Marshall Collins, Carlos Cruz, Stefan Eins, Maggie Ens, Melissa Gibbs, Rebecca Howland, Rick Prol, Miguelangel Ruiz, William Scott, and others, August 24-October 5.
Liz-n-Val " Resurrection: an Installation", October 26 - November 23.
Herman, Ed "From the Street to the Sky", October 26 - November 23.
1992
Coad, Wendy: Paintings, January 1 - February 28.
Ruiz, Miguelangel: Installation on the facade of Fashion Moda, January 10 - February 28.
One: Recent Paintings and other Works, exhibition of paintings by Stefan Eins, March -April.
VanArsdol, Robin: Paintings, May 11 - 25.
G. J. W. "Vulva", October 16 - November 7.
Paddock, Laura: Installation of the Facade, October 17 - Mid-November.
Ward, Seward: Sculpture, (n. d.)
Yarra, Melanie Claire: Paintings, (n. d.)
1993
Brunner, Norbert "Object/Space", May 15 - 29.
Schr, Beate Maria "Bodysuits", May 15 -29.
Exhibitions with year unknown:
Henriquez, Renny Molenaar "Eyes of Liberty", May 14 - June 4.
Provenance
The archive was built and preserved by Stefan Eins and others at Fashion Moda and acquired via purchase from Stefan Eins in March of 1999.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Content Note
The Fashion Moda Archive includes photographs, color slides, posters, flyers, announcements, press releases, magazine articles, reviews, grant proposals, video tapes, business files, artworks, and one audio tape. The archive was built and preserved by Stefan Eins and others at Fashion Moda. Oversized archival materials from the various series are located in three oversize boxes at the end of the archive and in the mapcase.
The Fashion Moda archive is comprised of business files, nearly 400 photographs of exhibitions and artists, approximately 3,200 35mm slides documenting exhibitions and other events, newspaper articles, reviews, grant proposals, artist resumes, correspondence, video tapes of the cable TV series "Making Coincidences", production materials relating to Fashion Moda's contribution to Documenta 7 in 1982, posters, flyers, and art work by Kenny Scharf, Jenny Holzer, Keith Haring, Charles Andre, Paulette Nenner, and Wendell Headley. A portfolio of artists prints produced by Fashion Moda is included in Series IIID. It consists of works by Ronnie Curtone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz. The scope of the archive is comprehensive in that it contains all records and files kept by Stefan Eins. As much as possible, his original organization of the material was preserved. Please note that you may need to look at more than one series - as listed below. Materials were grouped by format. Slides, press releases, flyers and other information about the same exhibition, event or artist may be in more than one series. Some cross referencing has been done, but it is not comprehensive.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
Series I: Fashion Moda Overview
Series I contains documents which were arranged by Fashion Moda's director Stefan Eins. The original intent of this grouping was for a proposal made to the Andy Warhol Foundation, with the intent that this history would be placed online. Therefore it has been left separated from the rest of the collection. This series contains slides, photographs, posters, magazine articles, and a selected bibliography. The files are kept in the original order as received by the Fales Library.
Series II: Fashion Moda as a business.
Series II is divided into two subseries and contains three boxes of documents. The files are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
Series II subseries A, Administrative Files, contains Fashion Moda's office records including: banking statements, mail lists, budgets, building leases, correspondence, financial reports, bills, renovation details, receipts, and taxes.
Series II subseries B, Grants and Fundraising, contains documentation of grant proposals and fundraising projects.
Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials.
Series III is divided into seven subseries and contains 18 boxes of documents. The files are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
Series III subseries A, Artists Files, contains files Fashion Moda kept on their artists and exhibitions including: resumes, exhibition proposals, plans for exhibitions, consignment forms, program reports, and production materials for exhibitions. Please note that not all of the artists included here actually showed at Fashion Moda.
Series III subseries B, Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements, contains articles, press releases, flyers and announcements for exhibitions at Fashion Moda.
Series III subseries C, Photographs, contains photographs covering exhibition openings, artworks, artists, Fashion Moda's neighborhood, and performances.
Series III subseries D, Artworks, contains artworks by Keith Haring, Andre Charles, Daze, Crash, Kenny Scharf, Koor, and others. Included here is the Fashion Moda Portfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz.
Series III subseries E, Printed Materials, contains magazines, journals, and catalogs on artists such as Mark Kostabi, Ron English, Nancy Stout, and Amy Chaiklin. These items were found in the collection and do not necessary pertain solely to Fashion Moda.
Series III subseries F, Slides, contains 13 boxes of slides covering Fashion Moda's exhibitions, artists, and slide presentations. Note the exhibition slides are arranged chronologically and the individual artist slides are alphabetical. Not all individual artists presented in the slide files have actually exhibited at Fashion Moda.
Series III subseries G, Video - Access Copies, contains VHS and DVD researcher access copies for Stephan Eins' "Making Coincidences" and other cable TV programs. Materials are arranged chronologically.
Series III subseries H, Video - Originals, contains original source tapes for Stephan Eins' "Making Coincidences", other cable TV programs, and various programs presented by Fashion Moda. Materials are arranged chronologically.
Oversize: Two flat oversize boxes and one over-oversize box at the end of collection contains oversize materials from Series I, II, and III.
Performance artists.; New York (N.Y.) |x Social life and customs |y 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) |x Social life and customs |x Pictorial works.; Art |x Finance.; Modernism (Art).; Art patronage.; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities).; Artists and patrons.; Art -- Exhibitions -- New York (State) -- New York.; Grant proposals.; Art |x Marketing.; Artists -- United States.; Art, Modern -- 20th century; Art |x Management.; Art |x Management |z United States; Art, Modern -- 20th century -- Exhibitions.; Punk culture -- New York (State) -- New York; Punk rock music.; Youth in art.; Slides (photographs); Posters.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Videocassettes.; Fliers (printed matter); Performance art -- United States.; Audiotapes.; Brochures.; Graffiti.; Drawings; Financial records; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Photography |v Exhibitions.; Photographs.; Postmodernism; Photography |x Exhibitions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Press releases.; Postmodernism (Literature) |z New York (State) |z New York.; New York (N.Y.).; Postmodernism (Literature); Reviews (document genre); Ahearn, John, 1951-; Chaiklin, Amy; Crash, 1961-; Eins, Stefan; English, Ron; Golub, Leon, 1922-2004; Haring, Keith; Holzer, Jenny, 1950-; Kostabi, Mark, 1960-; Scharf, Kenny; Wells, David (Bobcat Wells, David N.)
- Series I: Fashion Moda Overview
  Scope and Content note
  Series I contains documents which were arranged by Fashion Moda's director Stefan Eins. The original intent of this grouping was for a proposal made to the Andy Warhol Foundation, with the intent that this history would be placed online. Therefore it has been left separated from the rest of the collection. This series contains slides, photographs, posters, magazine articles, and a selected bibliography. The files are kept in the original order as received by the Fales Library.
  - Subseries A: General
    - Fashion Moda Historical Overview, 1998., cuid8752 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Fashion Moda concept [see also III. A. 4. 44], undated; cuid8753 (Box 1, Folder 1A.)
    - Schedules, dates [see also pages 20-29, III. A. 4. 41 and III. A. 5. 90-93], undated; cuid8754 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Fashion Moda Logo., undated; cuid8755 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Four language, posters, flyers, announcements [see also III. B. oversize 21. 14-18 and 25], undated; cuid8756 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Selected Bibliography, Webster, Sally, 1995., cuid8757 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Selected press., undated; cuid8758 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Various Fashion Moda artists, slides [see also slide show III. F. 15. 148], undated; cuid8759 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Chronological
    - Inaugural Show: "Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy" 1978 [see also I. 1. oversize 20. 7AAand 7AB], cuid8760 (Box 1, Folder 7A.)
    - Cooney, Robert "Por Exxon, for Kill", installation in Fashion Moda's window, 1978 [see also over oversize box 22], cuid8761 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ahearn, John: face castings, 1979, cuid8762 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ross, Ray: photographs of jazz artists, 1979., cuid8763 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Fekner, John: 1980., cuid8764 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - South Bronx Show, May 15 - June, 1980., cuid8765 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Institute for Appropriate Technology, Earth Day, May 24, 1980 [see also II. A. 2. 60 and III. A4. 8 and 9], cuid8766 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Times Square Show: group exhibition in abandoned massage parlor, June 1 - ?, 1980., cuid8767 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti Art Success for America, group exhibition, Oct. 18 - ?, 1980, [see also III. B. oversize 21. 14-16 and III. C. 6. 19], cuid8768 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The New Museum show "Events", December 13, 1980 - January 8, 1981 [ see also III. E. 6. 7], 1980 - 1981; cuid8769 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - California Bilboards, 1980 - 1981 [ see also III. C. 6. 7 and III. F. 15 slides 36-38], cuid8770 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Stein, Jehnifer: exhibition, 1981., cuid8771 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Evans, Joan: performance, summer 1981., cuid8772 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Eins, Stefan "Billard/Pool for Random Objects", November 1981. [see also oversize box 22 and III. A. 4. 36-37A,75,75A, also III. G. 16], cuid8773 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Joe [see also I. 1. 7 and III. B. 5. 13], undated; cuid8774 (Box 1, Folder 20A.)
    - Satanic Sisters: 1979 - ca 1982, cuid8775 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Gilded ornament from Satanic Sisters event, cuid8776 (Box 23)
    - Holzer, Jenny: 1979 - 1982. [see also oversize box 21 and III. C. 6. 23], cuid8777 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Documenta 7, Kassel, Germany: May 1982 [see also oversize box 21- No Duplication Allowed], cuid8778 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Berman, Doris Boris "Fotoaktion South Bronx/NY", xerox book, June 1982., cuid8779 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Show Bronx Show: group exhibition, June 26 - August 7, 1982., cuid8780 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Ratti, Anna "Endgame", installation, April 29 - September 1983., cuid8781 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Food for Soup Kitchens, October 1 - 15, 1983., cuid8782 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Lady Pink & Lady Heart: installation, November 9 - December 10, 1983., cuid8783 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Finn, David "Animal", installation and "The Name", catalog, 1984, cuid8784 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Science, Art, Design,Invention, Technology, Fantasy, a brochure: 1984 {see also III. A. 5. 109 and III. A. oversize 21. 114], cuid8785 (Box 1, Folder 29A.)
    - Pain and Pleasure, exhibition, Spring 1984, cuid8786 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Samuels, Melvin (NOC 167) "Masterworks, One Man Show", September 1984., cuid8787 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Poppitz, James: University of Colorado,1985 [see also I. 1. 33 and 34, also III. F. 10. 59], cuid8788 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Fahion Moda Benefit Portfolio, "6 Giants" collaboration and "Art for Money" benefit at "Art and Industrie" 1985/86 [see also III. A. 4. 11-14 and III. A. 5. 85], 1985-1986; cuid8789 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Of the Streets, touring exhibition, Colorado, 1984/85 [see also III. F. 9. 39, also III. B. oversize 21. 19-23 and III. C. 6. 6], 1984-1985; cuid8790 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Beyond Word, curated by Phase2, November 7 - December 7, 1987, cuid8791 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid8792 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Liz-n-Val "Resurrection", October 14, 1991., cuid8793 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Herman, Ed "From the Street to the Sky", October 26 - November 23, 1991., cuid8794 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Coad, Wendy & Laura Paddock, 1992., cuid8795 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Facades of Fashion Moda [see also III. B. 6. 16. A and III. F. 11. 70 and 74], undated; cuid8796 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Headley, Wendell., undated; cuid8797 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Straus, Sandy, undated; cuid8798 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Rivera, James., undated; cuid8799 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Schmidt, George., undated; cuid8800 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - G. J. W. "Vulva", October 16 - November 7, 1992 [see also III. B. oversize 21. 25 and III. C. 6. 52], cuid8801 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Van Arsdol, Robin., undated; cuid8802 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    Series II Subseries A, Administrative Files, contains Fashion Moda's office records including: banking statements, mail lists, budgets, building leases, correspondence, financial reports, bills, renovation details, receipts, and taxes.
    - Advertising receipt, 1985; cuid8803 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Pat: consulting, 1986; cuid8804 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Banking: Balances, 1990-1991; cuid8805 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Banking: Cancelled checks, 1987-1988; cuid8806 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Banking: Deposit slips, 1987-1988; cuid8807 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Banking: Savings account, 1987-1989; cuid8808 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Banking: Statements, 1987-1988; cuid8809 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Banking: Statements and cancelled checks, 1988-1989; cuid8810 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board meeting notes, 1977-1984; cuid8811 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bronx Museum of Art: mailing list, undated; cuid8812 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1984-1985; cuid8813 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Budgets, 1987-1989; cuid8814 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Building projects, 1988; cuid8815 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Capital improvement goals., undated; cuid8816 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Centrum Foundation., undated; cuid8817 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1976; cuid8818 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chase Manhattan, 1987; cuid8819 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chemical bank, 1984; cuid8820 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - City budget proposal: guide/booklet, 1988; cuid8821 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Building closing: 2754 Third Ave., 1993; cuid8822 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Building closing: 2754 Third Ave., 1993; cuid8823 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Con Edison: bills, 1985; cuid8824 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Con Edison: bills, 1987; cuid8825 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Contract, 1987-1988; cuid8826 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence from Stefan Eins, 1981-1989; cuid8827 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence to James Poppitz from Sabine Wewer, 1986-1987; cuid8828 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence to Stefan Eins from artists, 1981-1987; cuid8829 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence to Stefan Eins from artists, 1981-1984; cuid8830 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Fashion Moda address book, n. d., undated; cuid8831 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Fashion Moda: fundraising letter, 1985; cuid8832 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Fashion Moda: notebook, n. d., undated; cuid8833 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Fashion Moda: tull, 1984; cuid8834 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Financial report, 1979-1980; cuid8835 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Financial report, 1981-1982; cuid8836 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Financial report, 1982-1983; cuid8837 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Financial report, 1983-1984; cuid8838 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Financial report, 1984-1985; cuid8839 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Financial report, 1985-1986; cuid8840 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Financial report, 1986-1987; cuid8841 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Filing cabinet, painted, 1978-1993; cuid6055; 1 item one file cabinet (Item MSS.091.cuid6055)
      filing cabinets.
    - Financial report, 1987-1988; cuid8842 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Financial report, 1988-1989; cuid8843 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Funds received, 1980-1984; cuid8844 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - H. O. W. project account, 1987-1988; cuid8845 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Huntington Block Insurance., undated; cuid8846 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Insurance., undated; cuid8847 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Intern program., undated; cuid8848 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - I. R. S., 1979- 1989; cuid8849 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Job descriptions and contact for directors of Fashion Moda, August 12, 1987., cuid8850 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Lease: 2803 Third ave, Bronx, 1978- 1981; cuid8851 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Lease: 2803 Third Ave., Bronx (court case), 1983; cuid8852 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Lease: 2803 Third Ave., Bronx, 1985- 1988; cuid8853 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Lease: 2803 Third Ave., Bronx, 1987- 1994; cuid8854 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Letters of request, 1985; cuid8855 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Loan, 1983; cuid8856 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Mailing list., undated; cuid8857 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Mailing list., undated; cuid8858 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Mailing list: Bronx Museum & South Bronx Art Show, 1987; cuid8859 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Mailing list., undated; cuid8860 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Napoleon/Ward problem, 1986; cuid8861 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - New York City Audubon Society, 1979- 1984; cuid8862 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - The Fashion Moda urban hot water system by Jas Dziewanowski, undated; cuid8863 (Box 2, Folder 60A.)
    - New York Telephone: bills, 1986; cuid8864 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - New York State tax exempt status, 1985-1986; cuid8865 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Ongoing renovation: 2803 Third Ave., Bronx, 1986; cuid8866 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Ongoing renovation: 2754 Third Ave., Bronx, 1989-92. [also see oversize box 20], 1989-1992; cuid8867 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Orsman, Janet, 1985; cuid8868 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Outstanding debts., undated; cuid8869 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Payments to artists, undated; cuid8870 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Pearl Paint Company, undated; cuid8871 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Planning for trip., undated; cuid8872 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Potential board & advisors., undated; cuid8873 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Politics at Fashion Moda., undated; cuid8874 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Press List, 1985; cuid8875 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Print Portfolio, 1984; cuid8876 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Quinn & Poppitz fundraiser, 1987; cuid8877 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Real estate taxes, 1986; cuid8878 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Receipts, 1984- 1985; cuid8879 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Receipts, 1988- 1989; cuid8880 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Receipts for cash payments, January - August 1989., cuid8881 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Receipts from Aspen trip, 1984- 1985; cuid8882 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Receipts: shipping., undated; cuid8883 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - REM tax, 1986; cuid8884 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Resale tax certificate., undated; cuid8885 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Sales receipt book, 1985; cuid8886 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Scriptex/Ricoh., undated; cuid8887 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Slide fee, 1984; cuid8888 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Staff resumes., undated; cuid8889 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Stenographer bill, 1985- 1987; cuid8890 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Taxes, 1979- 1980; cuid8891 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Taxes, 1983- 1984; cuid8892 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Taxes, 1984; cuid8893 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Taxes, 1984- 1985; cuid8894 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Taxes, 1985- 1986; cuid8895 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Taxes, 1986; cuid8896 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Taxes, 1987- 1988; cuid8897 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Trash ticket., undated; cuid8898 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Typeset styles., undated; cuid8899 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - U. S. telecom., undated; cuid8900 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Urban corps., undated; cuid8901 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Water at Fashion Moda., undated; cuid8902 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - West 44th., undated; cuid8903 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Wexford press., undated; cuid8904 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising
    Scope and Contents note
    Series II Subseries B, Grants and Fundraising, contains documentation of grant proposals and fundraising projects.
    - Arts Forward fund, 1992; cuid8905 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1978-1981; cuid8906 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1984-1985; cuid8907 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1987-1988; cuid8908 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1993; cuid8909 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Chase Manhattan neighborhood grant, 1986-1987; cuid8910 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Colorado Council on the Arts and Humanities, grant application, 1984-1985; cuid8911 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Corporations approached for funding, 1980-1982; cuid8912 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, final report, 1985-1986; cuid8913 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, letters & voucher, 1980-1981; cuid8914 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, load fund application, 1989-1990; cuid8915 (Box 3, Folder 11)